[{"answer": "You know, when you talk to people here, and this sounds like cliche, but it is so true with everyone that I've spoken to that knows this young man.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Is there any indication at the moment about any motive for what happened?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Very few.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Yes, do the -- do the Bobbies carry guns now?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think they believe it as passionately as the right.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What's your sense?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Are you disappointed that Obama hasn't done something more concrete about guns?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "What made you get up one day and say I'm going to do this?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "I'm driving a cab at night now.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "How bad are you going to miss it, Bill?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Well, no, because it wasn't to him, it was to the super PAC.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Have you heard from the president since your donation?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "It's a silly argument.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Is it a silly argument?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, he would just -- he would out-and-out lose this election if he didn't -- .", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "That's still hypocrisy, isn't it?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Even if you think it's morally and ethically wrong?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, that's true.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "But given that Romney is out-spending all his competitors with these super PACs, and like 10-1 and he still isn't getting very far, certainly winning his election battle at the moment, what makes you think the super PACs are actually that effective?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Of course, every -- they always have.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Would every coach do that?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "He was crazy is what we would think.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "What would we think of a coach who didn't do that?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "But here's the problem.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "It's true, when Rick -- when Rick Santorum says, you know, Obama thinks that your -- I don't know what -- what did he say about Obama that he wants to rule over you?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "I don't think he read the speech properly because that's not what Kennedy was saying.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "How dare you say you won't be taking your orders from the Pope?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "It's similar to the silly thing about you -- the designated hitter and how that's a hypocrite.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "What do you think of that whole argument on both sides?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well, sometimes you do need a nanny state.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "How much should the government lead, and how much strays into nanny state, do you think?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Well, first, I would invest.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "If you were president, what are the three quick things that you would strive to do to put America back on its feet, do you think?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I hadn't seen that.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Did you find that funny or not?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "What's to get upset about?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Do you like him?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Well, he can.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Why can't he do it with his religion, if he believes?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "It is, of course.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "And actually, I suspect, do believe that it's perfectly acceptable for people of religious influence to work in politics as well and govern?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "If Jeremy Lin came to you and said, look, I want you to join me in prayer and I will score 20 more points against the Lakers, would you do it?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "No one -- Piers, I love the way people who are pro-choice find the most grotesque possible moral dilemma to set up one side or her to.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Would you simply have wanted -- not wanted, but have drawn the conclusion the only ethical or moral solution would be that the mother should die?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "I think it begins at conception.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Where do you think life begins?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Well, I guess I'll use the word guilty, or very, very happy.", "docId": "120227pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "How do you plead to that charge?", "qSentId": 613}]